https://www.prideofmanchester.com/privacy.htm

HOME | WHAT'S ON IN MANCHESTER |
MANCHESTER RESTAURANTS | MANCHESTER BARS | MANCHESTER HOTELS
SPECIAL OFFERS | MANCHESTER MUSIC | MANCHESTER THEATRES | CINEMAS | MANCHESTER UNITED | SUBSCRIBE
TOP 10 BEST RESTAURANTS IN MANCHESTER | TOP 10 BEST BARS IN MANCHESTER | TOP 10 BEST HOTELS IN MANCHESTER
PRIDE OF MANCHESTER
PRIVACY POLICY
This privacy policy covers the Pride Of Manchester Group of Websites:
~ HotelsOfManchester.com / OldTraffordHotels.com
Who Are We & What Data Do We Gather?
The Pride Of Manchester Group is based in Cheshire, United Kingdom. We are a stable of websites, dating back to 1999, which primarily inform our readers of entertainment events, restaurant and bar offers, reviews and news, as well as provide information on Manchester music, sports, history and literature.
Pride Of Manchester
is committed to user privacy and
you can browse through all of our Web Sites without giving any information about yourself. In some rare cases, personal information may be required in order to obtain a special offer or access to an event. This information is not stored afer the event and only shared, where specified, with the organiser/venue for the purposes of that offer/event.
We do not, ourselves, gather personal data from visitors to our site, other than giving the visitors the opportunity to subscribe to our newsletters, in which case we will require simply their first and last names, their preferred title and their email address. You can learn more about what we do with this information,
below.
Cookie Policy
If you choose to use the services of, or buy a product from, a Service Provider we link to, they will usually require more information and, like most websites, will often use cookies for analytical and affiliate tracking purposes. Where we link to a third party website, we would
encourage you to review their
cookie policy, as we do not control them.
Like most other websites nowadays, we use Google Analytics, a piece of software operated by Google that
leaves
cookies (tiny text files) within each user’s browser that
records data about the reader’s activity within our website. Google then use this information to provide us with
useful analytical reports that let us know which pages on the website are being visited, how long readers spend on the page and
which links they click on within it, amongst other information. It does not provide us with personal information about yourself.
You can disable the future use of cookies or delete any cookies already stored on your computer by using your browser settings or by clicking here for more info. Alternatively, you can
opt out of
many third-party vendor's use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page here. However, disabling or deleting cookies may prevent you from using certain functionality on our website or others using the same third party services.
Third Party Services, Affiliates & Websites
In most cases, we do not directly provide the leisure services and products which we advertise or promote. For example, we are not a ticket seller, restaurateur, reservation service,
theatre operator nor a booking agency. Instead,
we introduce our readers to specialist third party “Service Providers” which provide those services. We have no control over the services and websites of these
Service Providers, and our links are provided for your convenience only and, where necessary, for them to track our referral.
If you choose to use the services of, or buy a product from, a Service Provider we link to, they will usually require more information and, like most websites, will often use cookies for analytical and affiliate tracking purposes.
Our site, like most websites, includes functionality provided by third parties, such as embedded YouTube videos, Spotify playlists, Facebook comments boxes, Google Maps, or
restaurant booking consoles from OpenTable, Bookatable or LiveRes. These providers may also use cookies. Disabling these cookies will likely break the functions offered by these third parties.
Where following our links to a third party website or by using their embedded services, we would
encourage you to review the privacy and cookie policies
on their respective websites, as we do not control them.
On occasions,
Pride Of Manchester may display banner advertisements provided by the likes of Google Ads, Amazon or other affiliate networks, which may use cookies not visible to, nor under the control of our websites. These
third-party companies may use cookies to serve ads based on your past visits to our websites or any other which uses their services. You can find out more about Google Ads here.
We do not provide any warranty or guarantee concerning the information provided by third party Service Providers and cannot accept any liability associated with transactions made via their
websites or directly with them.
Pride Of Manchester Mailing List
Subscribers to our free opt-in e-mail mailing list, are only asked for their
preferred title, first and last names, together with their email address. This information is stored on the secure U.S. based servers of our email marketing and newsletter service provider, Campaigner.com (you can read their privacy policy here and their anti-spam policy here).
We do not normally require any additional information, although subscribers may, if they choose,
provide additional information to help us tailor the information which they receive from us.
Members are required to confirm their subscription request after opting in.
Subscription to our mailing lists is entirely optional and subscribers can unsubscribe and manage their settings at any time by a simple and transparent process, with links to do so clearly dispayed at the footer of each mailing.
We delete all information of any unsubscribed member within 3 months of them opting-out.
The unique links included in each mailing allow us to analyse what members click on, helping us improve the service we provide and tailor our emails to be of more interest to our membership.
We take our Privacy Policy seriously and you can rest assured that any information you provide to us is stored securely and will not be sold on or otherwise passed on to any third party.
Social Media
The Pride Of Manchester Group maintains accounts with social networking sites, Facebook, Twitter and Instagram. If readers choose to engage with us on any of these platforms, we would refer them to the individual privacy policies of the specific sites. As we have no control over their policies, we are unable to accept any responsibility for their actions.
Disclaimer
Our goal is to keep the information on our websites timely and accurate. If errors are brought to our attention, we will try to correct them immediately. However Pride Of Manchester accepts no responsibility or liability whatsoever with regard to the information on this site.
Whilst we try to display the most up to date information, this is
of a general nature only and is not necessarily comprehensive, complete, accurate or up to date. We sometimes link to external sites over which we have no control and for which Pride Of Manchester assumes no responsibility.
It is our goal to minimise disruption caused by technical errors. Pride Of Manchester accepts no responsibility with regard to such problems incurred as a result of using this site or any linked external sites.
Contact Us
For more information about our Privacy Policy, or for any other reason, feel free to contact us here.
[back to top]
Disclaimer: PrideOfManchester.com can not be held responsible for any differences experienced at the premises listed.
